[{"answer": " What are you having for lunch today, Will", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " I dont know.  Ill probably stop by McDonalds or Burger King.  What about you", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 14, "question": " What are you having for lunch today, Will", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " I brought a salad and some salmon.  You know, you really should try to ea", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 15, "question": " I dont know.  Ill probably stop by McDonalds or Burger King.  What about you", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " What do you mean?  Fast food is quick, delicious, and nutritious", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 19, "question": " I brought a salad and some salmon.  You know, you really should try to ea", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " It may be fast and taste good, but its not nutritious.  Its loaded with fat and i", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 20, "question": " What do you mean?  Fast food is quick, delicious, and nutritious", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Well, I dont seem to be putting on weight, so I dont need to worry", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 22, "question": " It may be fast and taste good, but its not nutritious.  Its loaded with fat and i", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " I dont think so, I mean a hamburger is just meat, lettuce, and tomato, and frenc", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Well, I dont seem to be putting on weight, so I dont need to worry", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Not quite.  They are fried and made with processed meat, so they have tons o", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 28, "question": " I dont think so, I mean a hamburger is just meat, lettuce, and tomato, and frenc", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": "You know, just cause youre not getting fat doesnt mean youre in good health", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Not quite.  They are fried and made with processed meat, so they have tons o", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Nah, Im fine", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 40, "question": "You know, just cause youre not getting fat doesnt mean youre in good health", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Whens the last time you had a check up", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Nah, Im fine", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Oh, its been a long time, but I feel fine.  Im not worried", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Whens the last time you had a check up", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Im just saying, youd better watch out", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Oh, its been a long time, but I feel fine.  Im not worried", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Yeah, yea", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Im just saying, youd better watch out", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Oh, you know what.  You really should see that documentary called Supe", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Yeah, yea", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " No, what is it", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Oh, you know what.  You really should see that documentary called Supe", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Its a film out about the fast food culture in the U.S. and the growing rate o", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 50, "question": " No, what is it", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Oh yeah", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Its a film out about the fast food culture in the U.S. and the growing rate o", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Yeah.  This guy decides to eat nothing for McDonalds for 30 days to see wha", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Oh yeah", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " You mean he just ate McDonalds for dinner every day", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Yeah.  This guy decides to eat nothing for McDonalds for 30 days to see wha", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " No, he ate there three times a day: for breakfast, lunch, and dinner", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 61, "question": " You mean he just ate McDonalds for dinner every day", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Thats a lot of McDonalds", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 62, "question": " No, he ate there three times a day: for breakfast, lunch, and dinner", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Yeah, it is.  Do you know what happened to him", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Thats a lot of McDonalds", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " He gained a few pounds", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Yeah, it is.  Do you know what happened to him", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Not just a few.  He gained almost 30 pounds", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 65, "question": " He gained a few pounds", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Oh", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Not just a few.  He gained almost 30 pounds", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Thats not all.  He started feeling really sick and doctors tested him and said h", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Oh", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " That sounds pretty serious", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Thats not all.  He started feeling really sick and doctors tested him and said h", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " It is.  I mean, that movie was a clear example of what eating fast food all th", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 75, "question": " That sounds pretty serious", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " That does sound kind of scary", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 79, "question": " It is.  I mean, that movie was a clear example of what eating fast food all th", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " It really is.  You really should see it.  Its a real eye-opener", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 80, "question": " That does sound kind of scary", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Maybe I will go see it", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 81, "question": " It really is.  You really should see it.  Its a real eye-opener", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " You should.  I think it will change the way you think about fast food", "docId": "10-08", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Maybe I will go see it", "qSentId": 81}]
